[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 1]
Liu Shao.
I want you to walk out of this yard
and do many great things.
But do you want to trade your fate for it?
Okay.
I promise you.
I will be here with you for three days
and do whatever you want.
No matter wherever you want to go,
I will take you there.
Wow.
It's been three days.
It's time to go back.
Can I see you again?
Ten years later,
If fate is not over,
we will eventually meet.
My Lady.
[Daughter of Liu family, Liu Shao]
I knew
you must have fallen asleep here.
[Maid of Liu family, Xiaolian]
Did you dream of
the immortal who had a promise and be with you for three days?
I know. You don't believe me.
My parents said
I slept under a pear tree for a while.
But
I did meet that immortal.
He said
he changed my fate.
Ten years later,
I will have
a completely different life.
Think about it.
It's been
over ten years.
My Lady,
I think you're just bored.
I don't know why Od Master
won't allow you to go out.
He told us
you will bring demons
when you go out.
Nonsense!
I won't bring demons.
My father said
I can go out
after my birthday tonight.
[Lu Sheng's Manor]
[Half Demon, Lu Sheng]
Enough.
You two go.
Li,
take a rest
and get ready for tonight.
[Jade Pavilion]
The immortal said
we will meet when I grow up.
I'm turning 18 today.
I'm a grown-up.
Maybe
I'll see the immortal soon.
Shao.
[Liu Shao's parents]
Father, Mother.
See.
These longans
are very fresh.
Shao,
you can go out
after today.
Are you happy about it?
You are the best to me.
What happened?
Shao, you...
It's the Mysterious Light.
What's going on?
Who is laughing?
Mother!
Help! Help!
Help!
What's going on?
Demons.
Don't come over!
I’m here.
Leave now!
[Demon King of the Land, Ao Hen]
Fairy.
Thank you for saving us.
Father.
She is not a fairy.
She is a big demon.
Big demon?
Big demon!
Protect Miss Liu! Hurry!
Hurry!
Protect Miss Liu!
Girl,
you know something.
You even know I'm
a big demon.
No wonder
you are the chosen one.
But from today onwards,
you
will belong to my son.
Hurry! Protect Miss Liu!
Be careful!
Run!
Run, Liu Shao!
Mother.
Come at me.
Don't hurt my family.
Mother.
Young girl,
you are quite bold.
Aren't you afraid of me?
I'm not afraid of you.
You can't kill me.
It's not the day.
I need to see the mountains, rivers,
and the stars of the world.
I won't be killed by you today.
Really?
Unfortunately, the Mysterious Light in your body
will bring disaster to you and your family.
You will be chased by the Demons.
Do you think you can still see the mountains and rivers?
Father, Mother.
Mother.
Who are you?
I hunt demons like you who bring disasters to the mortal world.
[Demon Hunter, Lu Li]
I'm a demon hunter, Lu Li.
Watch out!
You are as weak as an ant.
How dare you fight against me?
So what if I'm an ant?
Ants dare to tumble a tree
and the sky.
You ask for it.
Ao Hen.
Lu Sheng.
What are you doing here?
Long time no see.
Could it be...
this arrogant guy
is your disciple?
Listen.
Even with your formation,
this ant will die anyway.
Really?
Then please open your eyes and see
if he's an ant.
Impossible.
It can't be the power of a mortal.
It seems that
everything is going as expected.
[Mansion of Wu Yang Duke]
Last night, there was a sudden Mysterious Light.
I heard that the Mysterious Light attracted hundreds of demons.
Even the demon Ao Hen was there.
Is that true?
Yes.
She went for a girl named Liu Shao.
[Guard of Wu Yang Duke, Fang Zhan]
But Ao Hen
was defeated and left.
[Wu]
Chong,
go check it.
[Bird Demon]
Ao Hen showed up
and we can't just sit and watch.
If necessary,
[Eldest Disciple of Wu Yang Duke, Du Mingchong]
take this girl back to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke to and protect her.
Why hasn't he woken up?
Is he okay?
He was just exhausted.
He'll be fine after a sleep.
My Lady.
Someone from the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke is here.
Mansion of Wu Yang Duke?
Are they here to help us get rid of demons?
I'll check it out.
Let's go.
Does it hurt?
Actually,
I'm...
fine.
But Master,
you are really amazing.
How did you know
the big demon would show up here?
Li,
take this
talisman.
I will use the formation to help you.
You must protect Miss Liu.
Master.
Well.
She's just an ordinary girl.
I don't think
there's something special about Miss Liu.
These demons
valued her so much
and all ran after her.
I guess Ao Hen won't give up easily.
I need one more thing
to keep Miss Liu safe.
Go get it.
Do we need to
say goodbye to Miss Liu?
No.
Is your daughter a noble person?
How dare she keep Mr. Du waiting?
She will be right here.
Have some tea.
This is the best Biluochun tea.
Father.
Is someone from the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke here?
Mr. Du,
this is my daughter, Liu Shao.
Liu Shao,
this is Mr. Du from the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
He is the first disciple of Wu Yang Duke.
Mr. Du.
You are Liu Shao?
Was Ao Hen
here for you?
Yes.
How on earth did you
offend her?
I didn't.
If you didn't,
why did a demon like Ao Hen
come here
and try to kill an ordinary person like you?
Mr. Du,
please be reasonable.
A murderer kills people
and brings disasters to people.
It is the murderer who should be blamed.
Moreover,
I didn't offend her.
Even if I did,
do I deserve to be killed?
What do you mean?
Are you lecturing me?
-My lord. -I...
My lord.
My daughter has stayed at home for a long time. She didn't mean it.
Please forgive her.
Fine, you know the rules.
Mr. Du,
when can the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke catch
that big demon?
It's not easy
to catch such a big demon.
Okay.
I know
the situation here.
I will report it to my Lord.
How could you take the money and do nothing?
I thought you were a hero.
How dare you be rude to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke?
I won't argue with you
because of your father.
How dare you talk nonsense here?
Anyone who enters the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke
are the best.
The Mansion of Wu Yang Duke is the safest place
with the Protection Spell.
Can you go there?
Why not?
Listen.
I will walk into the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke
on my own.
Okay, I'll wait.
Let's go.
My lord.
Don't be angry.
My lord, please don't be angry.
My lord.
He called himself the first disciple of the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke?
He is nothing.
I think
Mr. Lu is 100 times better than him.
Of course.
Does Mr. Lu who appeared in front of you
look like the immortal you saw?
My Lady.
What are you thinking about?
Actually, he does.
How about
we
go find him together?
My Lady,
I was just saying.
Are you really looking for him?
How could Mr. Lu be an immortal?
I think he is.
Otherwise, how could he save me at that time?
The immortal said
he would come back when I grow up.
Didn't you say
he does business at Moon River?
Where is he?
I just heard about it.
Desserts.
If Old Master finds out,
I will be doomed.
Can you say something else?
My Lady.
All right.
Let's go over there
and then we will go home.
Catch the moon.
Don't miss it.
Don't miss this opportunity.
He's over there.
My Lady.
You really don't know how good this deal is.
It's only one tael.
You can't lose anything.
Wait for me.
Why are you here?
I'm going to catch the moon in the Moon River.
Are you going or not?
You must be Mr. Lu.
I've been looking for you.
Really?
Miss, why are you looking for me?
Because you saved me that day.
So today,
I'm here to thank you.
Where are you going?
I...
I'm going to catch the moon.
I only charge one tael.
Do you want to go with me?
Okay.
Let's go.
Let me ask you something.
Go ahead.
I have a friend.
She met an immortal ten years ago.
She said he descended from the sky
and brought her to fly to the sky.
You are well-informed.
Then,
have you seen an immortal before?
Your friend must have a dream.
I've only seen demons
with my master for these years.
All immortals are living in
the immortal world.
How can we meet them?
Maybe she had a dream.
Have you really never met an immortal?
Of course not.
If I can meet an immortal,
I'll let you know first,
okay?
By the way,
I don't know your name yet.
My name is Liu Shao.
Liu Shao?
The moon is on the tip of the willow.
That's a good name.
Didn't you say you want to catch the moon?
We're already on the moon.
Look.
Wow.
What a beautiful moon shadow!
I'm going to catch the moon.
Wait for me.
Okay.
Hello?
Are you okay?
I don't want the moon, okay?
Don't scare me.
Come up.
I found you a treasure
and you don't want it?
No.
Come down.
Why are you
all dry?
Are you okay?
I know the Water-repellent Spell.
I'm fine.
You said you're not an immortal?
Stop pretending.
This is it?
Such a big clam shell.
Are you kidding me?
Of course not.
Close your eyes.
Okay. I can't see.
All right.
Look.
So beautiful.
Wow.
What a beautiful bracelet.
Isn't it pretty?
But what about the moon?
Didn't you tell me
to catch the moon in the Moon River?
Is it
this?
Look carefully.
You are now on the moon.
And there is the starry sky.
Your life
should be wonderful.
You will see mountains, rivers
and the stars of the four seas.
Is it beautiful?
Take it off.
What?
I'm just showing you.
I'm going to sell it.
Don't cheat.
Oh, right.
This bracelet is amazing.
If you want to sell it,
why don't you sell it to me?
Miss,
this bracelet is unusual.
This bracelet is made by
the Lake Demon's one eye
to raise her children.
It was formed in the golden clams.
It's very expensive.
Don't think about it.
But
the winter is coming.
I'll talk to them then.
Don't dig another eye
for their children.
I will take the bracelet.
I will take the other eye of them too.
Miss,
this bracelet
is at price of their lives.
The price
is not low.
2,000 taels.
Miss, you...
5,000 taels.
That's the maximum I can afford.
Really.
That's all I got
this time.
Besides,
the money is with her.
I don't have any.
Who?
Miss Xiaolian?
Yes.
The one on the shore?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
It’s too late.
We can't keep her waiting.
By the way,
don't
take it off.
It can ward off evil spirits.
I'm back.
Master.
According to what you said,
I've given her the Lake Bracelet.
She was very happy.
She gave me some money.
I
bought you some good medicine.
It will definitely cure your cough.
How do you know
she would come to the Moon River to find me?
She also asked me about
the immortal.
However,
you told me
the IImmortal Palace
is no longer involved in mortal affairs.
They are all managed by the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
Judging from what she said,
maybe
she might have met the immortal.
Did you pretend to be an immortal
and cheat her?
Master.
Don't say that.
She came there herself.
I just took the opportunity.
You've prepared the Lake Bracelet
for ten years.
If you give it to her like this,
I have to sell her at a good price.
But Master,
why did you give her the Lake Bracelet?
You asked me
why Ao Hen came to Miss Liu.
Although she is a mortal,
she has strong spiritual power.
I don't know where she gets it.
[Jade Pavilion]
I just know
this power will awaken at her age of 18
and attract all demons.
With the protection of the Lake Bracelet,
ordinary demons
won't dare to approach her.
This bracelet can really ward off evil spirits.
After Ao Hen's attack this time,
she will definitely go to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke to hide.
With the Lake Bracelet,
she should be safe.
Master,
I think
you're unfair.
You arranged everything for this girl.
Please arrange something for me.
How about this?
I’m killing demons every day.
I can't rest for a day.
-And? -Okay.
Get rid of the scattered demons in the back mountain.
Gosh, I’m so tired.
How many demons am I going to hunt?
If I keep hunting like this, I'll never be able to finish it for the rest of my life.
I wonder if the girl has gone to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
How did you know I was going to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke?
You...
How did you find me?
Why are you so nervous?
We are destined to meet.
We can meet everywhere.
Am I right?
Oh no.
She's here to ask for money.
Why do you look like you did something wrong?
The bracelet you gave me
can really ward off evil spirits.
Of course.
It works.
This is the Lake Bracelet.
It's a good deal for 5,000 taels, okay?
Go to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke with me to learn.
I can add more money.
Why should I go to such a place
with a spoiled lady like you?
20,000 taels.
Are you going or not?
It's very tiring to go to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
25,000 taels.
Well,
you also know that
my master has a cough.
He needs me.
30,000 taels?
People in the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke
need to go out to catch demons.
My life will be in danger.
This cost is huge.
You must add 10,000 taels more.
Miss Liu,
I plan to
let Li go to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke with you tomorrow
to attend the recruitment competition tomorrow.
Okay.
Master,
if you want to arrange things for me,
can you come back a little later?
Wait until I negotiate the price.
Do you have a problem?
No.
Miss Liu,
please go back and rest.
Lu Li will pick you up tomorrow morning.
Mr. Lu, see you tomorrow.
I heard it with my own ears.
Liu Shao said she would leave tomorrow morning
to attend the recruitment competition
tomorrow.
Your Majesty.
Please spare me.
That's all I know.
I can keep investigating.
Your Majesty, please spare my life.
It seems
the tonic energy of Liu Shao
will be mine
soon.
Back then, I only killed a few people from the Immortal Palace.
Yin was badly injured by them.
Yin.
Yin, are you okay?
You can't escape.
[Son of Ao Hen, Ao Yin]
Although we escaped,
my son was seriously injured
and returned to the infant state.
I will help you catch Liu Shao
and pass the power in her body to you.
Pass my order.
I want that girl
won't be able to enter the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
Master,
your steamed pear soup is ready.
You're ready to go?
Don't worry.
I can live wherever I go.
I'm always ready.
But Master,
why do you want me to go to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke?
Li,
do you remember
the Moon Sword I mentioned to you?
Yes.
I remember what you said.
As long as the Moon Sword is pulled out,
I will know who I am.
[Moon Sword]
Li.
The Moon Sword is actually in the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
Now that the Mysterious Light has appeared,
it means it's time.
You have to protect Liu Shao.
She's the key to pull out the Moon Sword.
Damn Lu Li!
He promised to pick me up, but where is he?
I can't wait for him.
I can't miss the recruitment.
What's that sound?
Are you also going to the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke
for the competition?
-Yes. -Yes.
Yes, we are.
Let's go together.
-Sure. -Sure.
Please.
Okay.
I...
Where are they?
Where did the wind come from?
It's so sunny.
Why do I feel so cold on my back?
Aren't there many recruiters in the recruitment of the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke?
Why is there no one here?
[Mansion of Wu Yang Duke]
So this is the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
I'm here
without Lu Li.
-Miss, are you alright? -You...
Ignore her.
My name is Wang Jian.
I'm here to attend the competition.
Just like you.
My name is Liu Shao.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
What are you thinking?
He would have come if he wanted to.
Liu Shao.
Coming.
If fate is not over,
we will eventually meet.
I'll use these three days to verify
if you're the person I'm looking for.
This is unfair to you.
But this is the only way
to save the world.
Liu Shao,
your fate
has begun.
Unfortunately,
I can't see that day.
It's a plan for thousands of years.
Now it's time
to begin.
Master.
I had a dream.
I dreamed
I was flying with a girl in the sky.
Everything is just as the Supreme God said.
We've been waiting for ten thousand years.
Finally, everything is ready.
Master.
Where are you?